Kalvin Son

Senior full stack developer

Organized, collaborative, and highly skilled senior full stack developer with 10+ years of professional experience in dynamic and deadline-driven work environments. Self-motivated and self-taught professional who likes to solve problems. My repositories includes programming languages and tools such as ReactJS, Angular, VueJS, NodeJS, Laravel, CI, Ruby on rails, MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MSSQL, Gulp, SASS, LESS, theming with Material UI and Bootstrap, Apache and Nginx server configuration and more related to the Blockchain industry such as Solidity, Ethereum, Smart Contract, DeFi, NFT marketplace, Rust, Solana...



kalvinson961010@gmail.com



12136503336



77, Sin Fat Road, Hong Kong, New Territories, Hong Kong

SKILLS

MERN

MEAN

PHP

Laravel



Python

Ruby

MySQL

LANGUAGES

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Swimming

Tennis

Camping

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer Gohomly Inc

11/2015 - 09/2020

GoHomly is a new modern company with the goal of helping all types of real estate agents automate, modernize and fairly compete for that listing presentation. It offers a complete suite of services specifically designed to help new experienced listing agents modernize and simplify the home showing and selling process.

- Made a Content Management System to build magazine for properties
- Implemented multi-core system in Node.js backend just using Cluster
- Created a theme customizing bootstrap v4 using scss in React.js frontend
- Integrated Narrpr and other services to get the details and statistical reports for sales history
- Managed VPS server and installed CI/CD
- Installed Apache Reverse Proxy in order to launch a backend with subdomain

Full stack web developer Tensail Analytics

11/2020 - 07/2022

Tensail Analytics provides clients with unprecedented gaming industry expertise combined with a comprehensive customer focused vision. The combination of the two is unmatched within the gaming service provider marketplace.

Achievements/Tasks

- Scraped details of sports events, odds, box scores, match stats, leaderboards from espn, rivals, synergy, stats-ncaa, donbest, pgatour and more
- Provided expectations with several formats according to the license
- Analysed the data contents and made expectation for the future match results

Full stack developer Toptal

Toptal is an exclusive network of the top freelance software developers, designers, finance experts, product managers, and project managers in the world. Top companies hire Toptal freelancers for their most important projects.

- Building stable and maintainable codebases using ReactJS and Angular
- E-commerce development with Shopify, customizing preexisting themes
- VPS configuration and optimization (Apache and Nginx)

EDUCATION

Computer science and programming University of British Columbia

09/2010 - 09/2015

Courses

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Vancouver, BC V6T 1Z4, Canada